Ever since I was born, I was dope.
Popstar: Never Stop Never Stopping is a comedy,
music film directed by Akiva Schaffer.
When his new album fails to sell records, pop/rap superstar Conner4real goes into a
major tailspin and watches his celebrity high life begin to collapse.
He'll try anything to bounce back, anything except
reuniting with his old rap group The Style Boyz.
Conner Friel, played by Andy Samberg.
Owen Bouchard, played by Jorma Taccone.
Lawrence Dunn, played by Akiva Schaffer.
Paula Klein, played by Sarah Silverman.
Harry Duggins, played by Tim Meadows.
Deborah, played by Maya Rudolph.
Popstar: Never Stop Never Stopping is a 2016 American mockumentary musical comedy film directed by Akiva Schaffer
and Jorma Taccone from a screenplay written by and starring Andy Samberg, Taccone, and Schaffer.
The trio, collectively known as The Lonely Island, also
co-produced the film with Judd Apatow and Rodney Rothman.
Sarah Silverman, Tim Meadows, Imogen Poots, Joan Cusack, Maya
Rudolph, and Chris Redd appear in supporting roles.
The film was released on June 3, 2016, by Universal Pictures, and became a box-office
bomb, grossing just over $9 million against a budget of $20 million.
It received generally positive reviews from critics, and
has since developed a cult following.
The film explores themes of concert, musician,
pop star, celebrity, mockumentary.
The tone is lighthearted.